Pooja ji, for pick of the day I would
like to choose the insurance company ICICI LBA
GIC LED. Here we have seen that as per the
results of the stock, according to me,
in mid-October, after that a very
good move came in the stock and
after the same consolidation, we saw that it was a
breakout, but after that in the last 8 to 10
trading sessions, we saw that the stock is
trading between 1980 and 2020
and is consolidating, but from here I
feel that a new base is being formed
around 1970 1965 and as long as this zone holds,
on the upside,
targets of 2050 and 2070 can come in ICICI GI.
In ICICI LBD, the
opinion will be to buy from this level and on dip of 1990,
keep a stop loss of 1960 and there are two targets of 2050 and 2070.
Ok?  So this is your advice on ICI Lamb.